Guide to the Records of the Grey Art Gallery and Study Center RG.42.5
New York University Archives
- Series I: Exhibition Files, 1961-2004; 213494
  - House of Iran Exhibition, 1978 April-September; cuid2409; 214327 (Box I:3, Folder 15)
  - House of Iran Exhibition (1978 November 14-24), 1978 May-December; cuid2410; 214326 (Box I:3, Folder 16)
  - Turkish Show, 1978 December-1979 November; cuid2411; 214325 (Box I:3, Folder 17)
  - Balet/Palmer/Smyth Essays, 1978; cuid2412; 214324 (Box I:3, Folder 18)
  - Ann Lauterbach - Poems for Washington Place Windows, 1978 January 17; cuid2413; 214323 (Box I:3, Folder 19)
  - Tiffany - Burlingham Information, circa 1978-1979; cuid2414; 214322 (Box I:3, Folder 20)
  - Tiffany Bulletin, 1979; cuid2415; 214321 (Box I:3, Folder 21)
  - Tiffany - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1979 March-1980 March; cuid2416; 214320 (Box I:3, Folder 22)
  - Life -- "Atlantic" Wainwright Article, 1972-1979; cuid2417; 214319 (Box I:17, Folder 29)
  - Life -- Information and Publicity, 1978 March-1979 June; cuid2418; 214318 (Box I:17, Folder 30)
  - LIfe -- Manual, Circa 1979-1981; cuid2419; 214317 (Box I:17, Folder 31)
  - Life -- Miscellaneous, 1972-1979; cuid2420; 214316 (Box I:17, Folder 32)
  - Life -- Photograph Titles, 1979 May; cuid2421; 214315 (Box I:17, Folder 33)
  - Life -- Village Night, 1979 May-June; cuid2422; 214314 (Box I:17, Folder 34)
  - American Painting -- Artist File, 1979 June-1981 April; cuid2423; 214313 (Box I:18, Folder 1)
  - American Painting -- Fact Sheets, 1979; cuid2424; 214312 (Box I:18, Folder 2)
  - American Painting -- General, 1979 April-September; cuid2425; 214311 (Box I:18, Folder 3)
  - American Painting -- Miscellaneous, 1979 March-September; cuid2426; 214310 (Box I:18, Folder 4)
  - American Painting -- Opening September 11, 1979 May-October; cuid2427; 214309 (Box I:18, Folder 5)
  - American Painting -- Symposium (1 of 3), 1979 October; cuid2428; 214308 (Box I:18, Folder 6)
  - American Painting -- Symposium (2 of 3), 1979 October; cuid2429; 214307 (Box I:18, Folder 7)
  - American Painting -- Symposium (3 of 3), 1979 October; cuid2430; 214306 (Box I:18, Folder 8)
  - American Painting -- Traveling Reviews, etc., 1979 July-December; cuid2431; 214305 (Box I:18, Folder 9)
  - American Symbolist -- October 23 Opening, 1979 October; cuid2432; 214304 (Box I:18, Folder 10)
  - American Symbolist -- Corespondence, Circa 1976-1981; cuid2433; 214303 (Box I:18, Folder 11)
  - American Symbolist -- Correspondence (Photos), 1977 December-1980 February; cuid2434; 214302 (Box I:18, Folder 12)
  - American Symbolist -- Correspondence (Spencer Museum), 1977 January-1980 June; cuid2435; 214301 (Box I:18, Folder 13)
  - American Symbolist -- Fact Sheets, 1979; cuid2436; 214300 (Box I:18, Folder 14)
  - American Symbolist -- Miscellaneous, 1979 February-November; cuid2437; 214299 (Box I:18, Folder 15)
  - American Symbolist -- Pivar Notes, Circa 1977-1980; cuid2438; 214298 (Box I:18, Folder 16)
  - American Symbolist -- Press Releases, 1979 October-November; cuid2439; 214297 (Box I:18, Folder 17)
  - American Symbolist -- Research (1 of 2), 1978-1979; cuid2440; 214296 (Box I:18, Folder 18)
  - American Symbolist -- Research (2 of 2), 1972-1979; cuid2441; 214295 (Box I:18, Folder 19)
  - Charles Gleyre -- Acknowledgements, Circa 1978-1980; cuid2442; 214294 (Box I:18, Folder 20)
  - Charles Gleyre -- Correspondence (Hauptman-Scott), 1978 August-1980 July; cuid2443; 214293 (Box I:18, Folder 21)
  - Charles Gleyre -- Correspondence (Luthy-ProHelvetia), 1976 August-1981 July; cuid2444; 214292 (Box I:18, Folder 22)
  - Charles Gleyre -- Musee Cantonal Labels, Circa 1978-1981; cuid2445; 214291 (Box I:18, Folder 23)
  - Charles Gleyre -- Press Releases, 1980; cuid2446; 214290 (Box I:18, Folder 24)
  - Charles Gleyre -- Fact Sheets, 1980; cuid2447; 214289 (Box I:18, Folder 25)
  - Charles Gleyre -- Miscellaneous, 1977-1982 June; cuid2448; 214288 (Box I:18, Folder 26)
  - Charles Gleyre -- Robert R. Littman Miscellaneous File, 1977 August-1981 February; cuid2449; 214287 (Box I:18, Folder 27)
  - David Hockney -- Background, Clippings and Other Miscellaneous, 1977 May-1980 March; cuid2450; 214286 (Box I:18, Folder 28)
  - David Hockney -- Billboard, 1980 February-June; cuid2451; 214285 (Box I:18, Folder 29)
  - David Hockney -- Evening on Wheels Press Release, 1980; cuid2452; 214284 (Box I:18, Folder 30)
  - David Hockney -- Miscellaneous Information on Artist (1 of 2), 1978 March-1980 September; cuid2453; 214283 (Box I:18, Folder 31)
  - David Hockney -- Miscellaneous Information on Artist (2 of 2), 1978-1980; cuid2454; 214282 (Box I:18, Folder 32)
  - David Hockney -- Parade/Metropolitan Opera, 1981 February-March; cuid2455; 214281 (Box I:18, Folder 33)
  - David Hockney -- Press/Literature, 1978-1982 August; cuid2456; 214280 (Box I:18, Folder 34)
  - David Hockney -- Sale Items, 1970-1977; cuid2457; 214279 (Box I:18, Folder 35)
  - American Stereographs -- Correspondence and Other Miscellaneous, 1980 May-September; cuid2458; 214278 (Box I:18, Folder 36)
  - American Stereographs -- Fact Sheets, 1980; cuid2459; 214277 (Box I:18, Folder 37)
  - American Stereographs -- Press Releases, 1980; cuid2460; 214276 (Box I:18, Folder 38)
  - American Stereographs -- Publicity and Other Miscellaneous, 1979 April-1980 April; cuid2461; 214275 (Box I:18, Folder 39)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Audio Guide, Circa 1979-1980; cuid2462; 214274 (Box I:18, Folder 40)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Audio Guide (Braille), Circa 1979-1980; cuid2463; 214273 (Box I:18, Folder 41)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Audio Guide (Miscellaneous Research), Circa 1978-1980; cuid2464; 214272 (Box I:18, Folder 42)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Biographies, Circa 1978-1980; cuid2465; 214271 (Box I:18, Folder 43)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Background Material (1 of 2), 1977-1978; cuid2466; 214270 (Box I:19, Folder 1)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Background Material (2 of 2), 1977-1982; cuid2467; 214269 (Box I:19, Folder 2)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Deaf, 1982 April; cuid2468; 214268 (Box I:19, Folder 3)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Fact Sheets, 1980; cuid2469; 214267 (Box I:19, Folder 4)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Press Releases, 1980; cuid2470; 214266 (Box I:19, Folder 5)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Publicity Mailing Lists, Circa 1978-1980; cuid2471; 214265 (Box I:19, Folder 6)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Reference on Handicapped, 1973 December-1981 May; cuid2472; 214264 (Box I:19, Folder 7)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Research (1 of 2), 1976 August-1978 November; cuid2473; 214263 (Box I:19, Folder 8)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Research (2 of 2), 1975-1978; cuid2474; 214262 (Box I:19, Folder 9)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Responses to Susan Cuddeback (Research), 1976 March-1979 April; cuid2475; 214261 (Box I:19, Folder 10)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Robert Littman's File, 1976-1980; cuid2476; 214260 (Box I:19, Folder 11)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Sources of Information, Circa 1978-1980; cuid2477; 214259 (Box I:19, Folder 12)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Susan Cuddeback Summary, 1979-1980; cuid2478; 214258 (Box I:19, Folder 13)
  - Sheldon Levison (Sept. 3-7, 1980), 1965-1980; cuid2479; 214257 (Box I:19, Folder 14)
  - Sheldon Levison -- Press Releases, 1980 August; cuid2480; 214256 (Box I:19, Folder 15)
  - Grey Fall Schedule Press Release, 1980; cuid2481; 214255 (Box I:19, Folder 16)
  - Walter Gay -- Catalog, 1980 August-1982 February; cuid2482; 214254 (Box I:19, Folder 17)
  - Walter Gay -- Press Literature, 1979 April-1981 January; cuid2483; 214253 (Box I:19, Folder 18)
  - Walter Gay -- Research, 1978 February-1980 November; cuid2484; 214252 (Box I:19, Folder 19)
  - Walter Gay -- Research Trip to Paris, 1979 October-December; cuid2485; 214251 (Box I:19, Folder 20)
  - Sonia Delaunay -- Background and Drafts, 1980; cuid2486; 214250 (Box I:19, Folder 21)
  - Sonia Delaunay -- Boutique, 1977-1980; cuid2487; 214249 (Box I:19, Folder 22)
  - Sonia Delaunay -- Lecture Series, 1980-1981; cuid2488; 214248 (Box I:19, Folder 23)
  - Sonia Delaunay -- Press Literature, 1979 December-1981 February; cuid2489; 214247 (Box I:19, Folder 24)
  - Sonia Delaunay -- Robert Littman's File (Lists and Other Miscellaneous), Circa 1980; cuid2490; 214246 (Box I:19, Folder 25)
  - Advance Exhibit Schedule (Winter-Spring 1981), 1980; cuid2491; 214245 (Box I:19, Folder 26)
  - Court of Benin -- Miscellaneous, 1979-1981; cuid2492; 214244 (Box I:19, Folder 27)
  - Court of Benin -- Press/Literature, 1980 April-1981January; cuid2493; 214243 (Box I:19, Folder 28)
  - Italian Dwarings -- Long Island Tour, 1980-1981; cuid2494; 214242 (Box I:19, Folder 29)
  - Italian Drawings -- Press, 1980-1981; cuid2495; 214241 (Box I:19, Folder 30)
  - Tracking the Marvelous -- Catalog, Circa 1980-1981; cuid2496; 214240 (Box I:19, Folder 31)
  - Tracking the Marvelous -- Catalog (John Myers Essay), Circa 1980-1981; cuid2497; 214239 (Box I:19, Folder 32)
  - Tracking the Marvelous -- Correspondence, 1980 October-1981 July; cuid2498; 214238 (Box I:19, Folder 33)
  - Tracking the Marvelous -- John Myers Press/Literature, 1979 November-1981 July; cuid2499; 214237 (Box I:19, Folder 34)
  - Tracking the Marvelous -- Press Release, 1981; cuid2500; 214236 (Box I:19, Folder 35)
  - Space Photography -- Book (1 of 2), 1978-1981; cuid2501; 214235 (Box I:19, Folder 36)
  - Space Photography -- Book (2 of 2), 1982; cuid2502; 214234 (Box I:19, Folder 37)
  - Space Photography -- Catalogue, 1980-1981; cuid2503; 214233 (Box I:19, Folder 38)
  - Space Photography -- Catalogue and Other Miscellaneous, 1981; cuid2504; 214232 (Box I:19, Folder 39)
  - Photography of Space -- French Research, Circa 1980-1981; cuid2505; 214231 (Box I:19, Folder 40)
  - Space Photography -- Image Requests (JPL), 1981 January-June; cuid2506; 214230 (Box I:19, Folder 41)
  - Space Photography -- Motorola, 1979-1982 May; cuid2507; 214229 (Box I:19, Folder 42)
  - Photography of Space -- Note Cards, 1981; cuid2508; 214228 (Box I:19, Folder 43)
  - Space Photography -- Photo Captions, 1981; cuid2509; 214227 (Box I:19, Folder 44)
  - Space Photography -- Photos, 1981 January-April; cuid2510; 214226 (Box I:19, Folder 45)
  - Space Photography -- Press/Literature (1 of 3), 1976-1981; cuid2511; 214225 (Box I:19, Folder 46)
  - Space Photography -- Press/Literature (2 of 3), 1979 August-1981 August; cuid2512; 214224 (Box I:20, Folder 1)
  - Space Photography -- Press/Literature (3 of 3), 1979 December-1983 January; cuid2513; 214223 (Box I:20, Folder 2)
  - Space Photography -- Press Release, 1981 June-December; cuid2514; 214222 (Box I:20, Folder 3)
  - Sesquicentennial Celebration -- Advance and Press Release, 1981; cuid2515; 214221 (Box I:20, Folder 4)
  - Sesquicentennial Celebration -- Andre Kertesz (Photo Copies), Circa 1980-1981; cuid2516; 214220 (Box I:20, Folder 5)
  - Sesquicentennial Celebration -- Andre Kertesz (Gallatin Ass.), 1980-1983; cuid2517; 214219 (Box I:20, Folder 6)
  - Sesquicentennial Celebration -- Brademas Collection, 1981; cuid2518; 214218 (Box I:20, Folder 7)
  - Sesquicentennial Celebration -- Miscellaneous, 1976-1981; cuid2519; 214217 (Box I:20, Folder 8)
  - Sesquicentennial Celebration -- Planning and General Memos, 1980-1981; cuid2520; 214216 (Box I:20, Folder 9)
  - Sesquicentennial Celebration -- Ralph Fasanella, 1980-1981; cuid2521; 214215 (Box I:20, Folder 10)
  - Tanya Grosman (Small Gallery), 1981 April-1982 August; cuid2522; 214214 (Box I:20, Folder 11)
  - Krasner/Pollock -- Book Draft 2, Circa 1979-1982; cuid2523; 214213 (Box I:20, Folder 12)
  - Krasner/Pollock -- Brochure, 1981; cuid2524; 214212 (Box I:20, Folder 13)
  - Krasner/Pollock -- Catalog, 1981; cuid2525; 214211 (Box I:20, Folder 14)
  - Krasner/Pollock -- Description of Exhibition, Circa 1979-1981; cuid2526; 214210 (Box I:20, Folder 15)
  - Krasner/Pollock -- Installation Layout, CIrca 1980-1981; cuid2527; 214209 (Box I:20, Folder 16)
  - Krasner/Pollock -- Pollock Beauborg Trip (Pompideau, France), 1981-1982; cuid2528; 214208 (Box I:20, Folder 17)
  - Krasner/Pollock -- Press/Literature (1 of 2), 1979-1982; cuid2529; 214207 (Box I:20, Folder 18)
  - Krasner/Pollock -- Press/Literature (2 of 2), 1979-1982; cuid2530; 214206 (Box I:20, Folder 19)
  - Krasner/Pollock -- Works in Exhibition and Values, 1980 February-1981 June; cuid2531; 214205 (Box I:20, Folder 20)
  - Ridiculous Theater, 1981; cuid2532; 214204 (Box I:20, Folder 21)
  - Chris Wilmarth (Exhibition Not Held), 1980 December-1981 December; cuid2533; 214203 (Box I:20, Folder 22)
  - Judson Dance Theater -- Bennington College, Circa 1980-1982; cuid2534; 214202 (Box I:20, Folder 23)
  - Judson Dance Theater -- Final NYSCA Presentation (Visual Material), 1981-1982; cuid2535; 214201 (Box I:20, Folder 24)
  - Judson Dance Theater -- Press Releases, Circa 1981-1982; cuid2536; 214200 (Box I:20, Folder 25)
  - Burra and Nash (3 British Painters) -- Press Literature, 1978-1982; cuid2537; 214199 (Box I:20, Folder 26)
  - Burra and Nash (3 British Painters) -- Catalog (1 of 2), 1981-1982; cuid2538; 214198 (Box I:20, Folder 27)
  - Burra and Nash (3 British Painters) -- Catalog (2 of 2), 1978-1982; cuid2539; 214197 (Box I:20, Folder 28)
  - Burra and Nash (3 British Painters) -- Press Releases, Circa 1981-1982; cuid2540; 214196 (Box I:20, Folder 29)
  - Burra and Nash (3 British Painters) -- Audio Cassette (Ker-Seymer, Billy Chappell), 1980 July; cuid2541; 214195 (Box I:20, Folder 30)
  - Burra and Nash (3 British Painters) -- Check List for Photographs, Circa 1981-1982; cuid2542; 214194 (Box I:20, Folder 31)
  - Miscellaneous Grey Press and Printed Material, 1985-1988; cuid2543; 214193 (Box I:20, Folder 32)
  - Stewart Wilson, 1981; cuid2544; 214192 (Box I:3, Folder 23)
  - Edward Henderson, 1981-1982; cuid2545; 214191 (Box I:3, Folder 24)
  - Around the Square (1 of 2), 1979-1980; cuid2546; 214190 (Box I:3, Folder 25)
  - Around the Square (2 of 2), 1979-1980; cuid2547; 214189 (Box I:3, Folder 26)
  - Around the Square -- Old Photographs and Curatorial Notes, circa 1980-1982; cuid2548; 214188 (Box I:3, Folder 27)
  - Around the Square -- Press/Literature (1 of 3), 1980-1982; cuid2549; 214187 (Box I:3, Folder 28)
  - Around the Square -- Press/Literature (2 of 3), 1980-1982; cuid2550; 214186 (Box I:3, Folder 29)
  - Around the Square -- Press/Literature (3 of 3), 1980-1982; cuid2551; 214185 (Box I:3, Folder 30)
  - Around the Square -- Correspondence, 1980 June-1982 June; cuid2552; 214184 (Box I:3, Folder 31)
  - Around the Square -- Window Installations (1 of 2), 1981-1982; cuid2553; 214183 (Box I:3, Folder 32)
  - Around the Square -- Window Installations (2 of 2), 1981-1982; cuid2554; 214182 (Box I:3, Folder 33)
  - Around the Square -- Mindy Cantor, 1981 April-1982 October; cuid2555; 214181 (Box I:3, Folder 34)
  - Around the Square -- Applebaum, 1981 December 3-1982 January 12; cuid2556; 214180 (Box I:3, Folder 35)
  - Around the Square -- Walking Tours, 1982; cuid2557; 214179 (Box I:3, Folder 36)
  - Around the Square -- PR Information, 1982; cuid2558; 214178 (Box I:3, Folder 37)
  - Bill Komosky, 1982 March-August; cuid2559; 214177 (Box I:3, Folder 38)
  - Audubon -- Exhibition Research (Inquiries to Owners), 1981-1982; cuid2560; 214176 (Box I:3, Folder 39)
  - Audubon -- General Correspondence, 1982; cuid2561; 214175 (Box I:3, Folder 40)
  - John James Audubon and His Sons - Final NYSCA Presentation, 1982 March-May; cuid2562; 214174 (Box I:3, Folder 41)
  - Audubon -- Magazine, 1982 January-February; cuid2563; 214173 (Box I:3, Folder 42)
  - Audubon -- PR, 1982 January-1983 June; cuid2564; 214172 (Box I:3, Folder 43)
  - Hare/Kiesler -- Press Photos, 1982; cuid2565; 214171 (Box I:3, Folder 44)
  - Hare/Kiesler -- Two Installations, 1982 April-June; cuid2566; 214170 (Box I:3, Folder 45)
  - Hare/Kiesler -- Publicity/Biographical Information, 1979 February-1983 January; cuid2567; 214169 (Box I:3, Folder 46)
  - Morse -- Packets of Reviews, 1982 July-1983 October; cuid2568; 214168 (Box I:3, Folder 47)
  - Morse -- Promotion, 1982 July-1983 January; cuid2569; 214167 (Box I:3, Folder 48)
  - Morse -- Photographs, 1982 June 17-1984 September 7; cuid2570; 214166 (Box I:3, Folder 49)
  - Morse -- Paul J. Strati, undated; cuid2571; 214165 (Box I:3, Folder 50)
  - Morse -- Lectures and Gallery Talks, 1982 September-1983 March; cuid2572; 214164 (Box I:3, Folder 51)
  - Morse -- Negatives of Text Labels, 1982-1983; cuid2573; 214163 (Box I:3, Folder 52)
  - Morse -- Works Not in Exhibition, 1982 August-1983 January; cuid2574; 214162 (Box I:3, Folder 53)
  - Morse -- Paul Stati, 1980 November-1983 December; cuid2575; 214161 (Box I:3, Folder 54)
  - Morse -- Benefit Preview, 1982 September; cuid2576; 214160 (Box I:3, Folder 55)
  - Morse -- Benefit Opening and Viewing, 1982 August-September; cuid2577; 214159 (Box I:3, Folder 56)
  - Morse -- Research, 1834-1872; cuid2578; 214158 (Box I:3, Folder 57)
  - Morse -- Correspondence, 1980 July-1984 March; cuid2579; 214157 (Box I:3, Folder 58)
  - Faces -- Bob's File, 1982-1983; cuid2580; 214156 (Box I:4, Folder 1)
  - Portrait Photography PR, 1982 August-November; cuid2581; 214155 (Box I:4, Folder 2)
  - Face to Face, 1981 February-1983 January; cuid2582; 214154 (Box I:4, Folder 3)
  - Faces Photographed, 1982 October-November; cuid2583; 214153 (Box I:4, Folder 4)
  - Frida Kahlo Information, undated; cuid2584; 214152 (Box I:4, Folder 5)
  - Kahlo/Modotti -- Publicity Photographs, undated; cuid2585; 214151 (Box I:4, Folder 6)
  - Kahlo/Modotti -- Whitechapel Correspondence, 1981 October-1983 March; cuid2586; 214150 (Box I:4, Folder 7)
  - Kahlo/Modotti -- at Whitechapel Art Gallery, 1982; cuid2587; 214149 (Box I:4, Folder 8)
  - Kahlo/Modotti -- Labels, circa 1982-1983; cuid2588; 214148 (Box I:4, Folder 9)
  - Kahlo/Modotti -- Catalog and Reproductions (1 of 2), 1982-1983; cuid2589; 214147 (Box I:4, Folder 10)
  - Kahlo/Modotti -- Catalog and Reproductions (2 of 2), 1982-1983; cuid2590; 214146 (Box I:4, Folder 11)
  - Kahlo/Modotti -- General Correspondence, 1982 January-1983 September; cuid2591; 214145 (Box I:4, Folder 12)
  - Kahlo/Modotti -- PR (1 of 2), 1982 March-1983 October; cuid2592; 214144 (Box I:4, Folder 13)
  - Kahlo/Modotti -- PR (2 of 2), 1982 March-1983 October; cuid2593; 214143 (Box I:4, Folder 14)
  - Bob's File -- Kahlo/Modotti, 1982 July-1983 January; cuid2594; 214142 (Box I:4, Folder 15)
  - Kahlo/Modotti -- Press Release and Exhibition Description, 1983; cuid2595; 214141 (Box I:4, Folder 16)
  - Kahlo/Modotti -- Review Packets, 1983 March-April; cuid2596; 214140 (Box I:4, Folder 17)
  - Kahlo/Modotti -- Photographs, 1985 June-July; cuid2597; 214139 (Box I:4, Folder 18)
  - Bergdorf/Montana Committee and Publicity, 1983; cuid2598; 214138 (Box I:4, Folder 19)
  - Bob's Bergdorf/Montana, 1982-1983; cuid2599; 214137 (Box I:4, Folder 20)
  - Turkish Exhibition -- AXIA, 1977-1983; cuid2600; 214136 (Box I:4, Folder 21)
  - Turkish Exhibition, 1979 March-1983 August; cuid2601; 214135 (Box I:4, Folder 22)
  - Ottoman Show -- Label Copy, circa 1982-1983; cuid2602; 214134 (Box I:4, Folder 23)
  - Turkish Exhibition -- Items (1 of 2), circa 1982-1983; cuid2603; 214133 (Box I:4, Folder 24)
  - Turkish Exhibition -- Items (2 of 2), circa 1982-1983; cuid2604; 214132 (Box I:4, Folder 25)
  - Bob's File - TAT (Turkish Exhibit), 1982 July-1983 August; cuid2605; 214131 (Box I:4, Folder 26)
  - Turkish Exhibition -- Object List from AIXA, 1982 December; cuid2606; 214130 (Box I:4, Folder 27)
  - Ottoman Show and Reception PR and Invitation, 1982 December-1983 June; cuid2607; 214129 (Box I:4, Folder 28)
  - Petropoulos Papers [Turkish Exhibition], 1983 April-1984 January; cuid2608; 214128 (Box I:4, Folder 29)
  - Abby Weed Grey Exhibit -- Press Photos, circa 1983; cuid2609; 214127 (Box I:4, Folder 30)
  - Paul Outerbridge -- Description, undated; cuid2610; 214126 (Box I:4, Folder 31)
  - Paul Outerbridge -- Correspondence, 1981 July-1984 March; cuid2611; 214125 (Box I:4, Folder 32)
  - Paul Outerbridge -- Press, 1982 February-1983 October; cuid2612; 214124 (Box I:4, Folder 33)
  - Eva Hesse -- Press and PR (1983), 1979-1983; cuid2613; 214123 (Box I:4, Folder 34)
  - Eva Hesse, 1983; cuid2614; 214122 (Box I:4, Folder 35)
  - Louise Dahl -- Wolfe Press, 1953-1983 December; cuid2615; 214121 (Box I:4, Folder 36)
  - Louise Dahl -- Wolfe Installation, 1983; cuid2616; 214120 (Box I:4, Folder 37)
  - Louise Dahl -- Wolfe RRL File, 1983; cuid2617; 214119 (Box I:4, Folder 38)
  - Dahl-Wolfe -- Interview, 1982 December 9; cuid2618; 214118 (Box I:4, Folder 39)
  - Louise Dahl-Wolfe -- Interview (Cassette), 1982 December 9; cuid2619; 214117 (Box I:4, Folder 40)
  - Louise Dahl-Wolfe -- Correspondence, 1982 May - 1983 September; cuid2620; 214116 (Box I:4, Folder 41)
  - Louise Dahl-Wolfe -- Dinner, 1983 August - September; cuid2621; 214115 (Box I:4, Folder 42)
  - Louise Dahl-Wolfe -- Magazine, 1981 June; cuid2622; 214114 (Box I:4, Folder 43)
  - Louise Dahl-Wolfe -- Staley-Wise Press Release, circa 1983; cuid2623; 214113 (Box I:4, Folder 44)
  - Permament Art Collection Exhibit, 1983; cuid2624; 214112 (Box I:4, Folder 45)
  - Permanent Art Collection Exhibit -- Labels, 1983; cuid2625; 214111 (Box I:4, Folder 46)
  - Ken Tisa, 1983 November; cuid2626; 214110 (Box I:4, Folder 47)
  - Picasso -- Hockney Essay, undated; cuid2627; 214109 (Box I:4, Folder 48)
  - Picasso -- Schiff Essay, Undated; cuid2628; 214108 (Box I:5, Folder 1)
  - Picasso -- Schiff, 1984 May-June; cuid2629; 214107 (Box I:5, Folder 2)
  - Picasso -- Catalogue, 1983; cuid2630; 214106 (Box I:5, Folder 3)
  - Picasso -- Publications, 1983-1984; cuid2631; 214105 (Box I:5, Folder 4)
  - Picasso -- Press, 1983 June-November; cuid2632; 214104 (Box I:5, Folder 5)
  - Picasso -- Proposal (Various Drafts), circa 1982-1983; cuid2633; 214103 (Box I:5, Folder 6)
  - Picasso -- Acknowledgements, circa 1982-1984; cuid2634; 214102 (Box I:5, Folder 7)
  - Bay Area Painting -- Krannert Art Museum, 1961; cuid2635; 214101 (Box I:5, Folder 8)
  - Bay Area Painting -- Exhibition, 1983 September-1984 June; cuid2636; 214100 (Box I:5, Folder 9)
  - Bay Area Painting -- Installation, circa 1984; cuid2637; 214099 (Box I:5, Folder 10)
  - Bay Area Painting -- Bob's File, 1983 December-1984 March; cuid2638; 214098 (Box I:5, Folder 11)
  - Bay Area Painting -- Correspondence to Newport Harbor, 1984 February-May; cuid2639; 214097 (Box I:5, Folder 12)
  - Bay Area Painting -- Northern California Figs. (Press; 1 of 2), 1979 June-1981 July; cuid2640; 214096 (Box I:5, Folder 13)
  - Bay Area Painting -- Northern California Figs. (Press; 2 of 2), 1979 October-1984 July; cuid2641; 214095 (Box I:5, Folder 14)
  - Bay Area Painting -- North California Figs. (Correspondence), 1980 February-1984 January; cuid2642; 214094 (Box I:5, Folder 15)
  - Bay Area Painting -- Joan Brown (Hansen Fuller Goldeen Gallery), 1978-1982 May; cuid2643; 214093 (Box I:5, Folder 16)
  - Bay Area Painting -- Catalogue, 1984 January-March; cuid2644; 214092 (Box I:5, Folder 17)
  - Bay Area Painting/Northern California Figs. -- Nathan Oliveira, 1980; cuid2645; 214091 (Box I:5, Folder 18)
  - Bay Area Painting/North California -- Action/Precision Catalogue, 1983-1984 January 25; cuid2646; 214090 (Box I:5, Folder 19)
  - Bay Area Painting -- Checklist, 1984 February-May; cuid2647; 214089 (Box I:5, Folder 20)
  - Jean Cocteau -- Paris, May 1983, After 1915; cuid2648; 214088 (Box I:5, Folder 21)
  - Jean Cocteau -- Paris, May 1983(Littman and McCready), 1983 March-May; cuid2649; 214087 (Box I:5, Folder 22)
  - Cocteau -- Invitation(Hill and Knowlton), Circa 1981-1984; cuid2650; 214086 (Box I:5, Folder 23)
  - Jean Cocteau -- Correspondence (1 of 3), 1983 August-December; cuid2651; 214085 (Box I:5, Folder 24)